https://www.womentc.com/privacy-policy/

About UsAbout UsOur TeamLocation & DirectionsWhy Choose Us?Frequently Asked QuestionsInsurance & PaymentInsurancePaymentCreative FinancingTestimonialsThank You CardsMedia, Publications, Speaking EngagementsVaginismus & TreatmentConditions & TreatmentsConditions & TreatmentsPenetration/Pain Disorders Painful Sex (Dyspareunia) Menopause & Painful Sex Vulvodynia Treatment for Vulvar VestibulitisSexual DysfunctionPelvic Floor Dysfunction Incontinence Bowel Dysfunction Organ ProlapseCancer Breast Cancer Female (Gynecologic) Cancer Cancer ResourcesAdditional Services PsychotherapyFor ProfessionalsFor ProfessionalsMaking a ReferralFemale Sexual DysfunctionMedia, Publications, Speaking EngagementsBlog & NewsBlog & NewsBleeding with sex (intercourse)Suffering in silence with painful intercourseVaginismus: is something (not) wrong with my vagina?Vaginismus and hymenDilators and Lidocaine for treatment of vaginismusMore Blog & News Articles...StoreStorePrivate PainPocket RocketParting the Curtains: A Woman's Handbook of Sex and SexualityContact UsSearch
Search
Search Home » Privacy Policy Contact Us:
Share this page:
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (www.womentc.com). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site and notifies you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Read our HIPAA Notice of Privacy Practice.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request to be in compliance with HIPAA and/or fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order, email you an invoice, confirm appointment, etc. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or patient treatment) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment and are password-protected.  Our entire staff undergoes HIPPA training as often as needed.Subscribe to our BlogReceive updates from the Women's Therapy Center blog in your inbox.
Email
Blog CategoriesGeneralMassageMenopause & Painful SexPainful Sex (Dyspareunia)Pelvic Floor DysfunctionPsychotherapySexual DysfunctionVaginismusVulvar VestibulitisVulvodyniaWomen's healthYear Cured
